<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Things that Suck </title>
		<link>/</link>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<author>Baron Schwartz</author>
		<rights>Copyright (c) 2018</rights>
		<updated>2018-09-03 00:00:00 &#43;0000 UTC</updated>
		
		<item>
			<title>Bananas</title>
			<link>/bananas/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
			<author>Baron Schwartz</author>
			<guid>/bananas/</guid>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;So disgusting I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure how it qualifies as a fruit. I hate them because:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The texture is absolutely awful&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;They go brown and mushy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Are often infested with fruit flies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I gag when I eat them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Worst fruit ever &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;blech&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Aingoo Large Writing Desk with Drawer 43x22 Rustic Computer Desk Slim Metal MDF Wood Grain Workstation for Brown Farmhouse</title>
			<link>/crappy-desk/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
			<author>Baron Schwartz</author>
			<guid>/crappy-desk/</guid>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;This desk was terrible. Screw holes did not line up and the wood felt and looked like plastic. If it&amp;rsquo;s too good to be true (like a $100 price tag for a reasonable desk) then it probably is. Sent this pile of junk back the same day we got it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Arctix Snowpants</title>
			<link>/snowpants/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
			<author>Baron Schwartz</author>
			<guid>/snowpants/</guid>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;What was I thinking&amp;hellip; Snowpants for $29. I spent a season snowboarding with a wet ass because every time I sat on a chair lift the snow would just soak through. I probably bought an extra $100 in whiskey trying to warm up after being completely soaked. Not worth it! Hate them!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Being Bald</title>
			<link>/bald/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
			<author>Baron Schwartz</author>
			<guid>/bald/</guid>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Okay, don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, there are definite advantages to being bald. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to mess around with hair products, you never have a bad hair day, and being shiny is quite nice. That being said, when it rains, you have no hair to absorb the water so the rain just streams into your face. That sucks. Also, in the summer you always have to put suntan lotion on your head (a peeling head is gross). Last, unless you are into comb overs there&amp;rsquo;s the shaving - it&amp;rsquo;s like you have twice the amount of face to deal with. Weighing it all up, and considering that if you have hair you can always shave it, I would have to say that being bald is at least 50% suck-o-meter worthy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Fishing off of a dock</title>
			<link>/fishing/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
			<author>Baron Schwartz</author>
			<guid>/fishing/</guid>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Ok&amp;hellip; first&amp;hellip; worms.. enough said. Second, if you catch anything you have to deal with a slimy stinky fish that will make your hands smell for days. Last, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it is about fishing off of a dock, but there always seems to be an old person lurking that wants to come over to ask if you&amp;rsquo;ve caught anything which of course turns into what feels like an eternity of painful conversation. Thumbs down to fishing off of a dock.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Phiaton BT 460 Black Wireless Touch Interface Headphones with Microphone</title>
			<link>/headphones/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
			<author>Baron Schwartz</author>
			<guid>/headphones/</guid>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;I think I got suckered by one of those fake review sites that are put up by people trying to make money through affiliate programs. The wired connection stopped working after a few months, and then the headband snapped. Truthfully, I was kinda glad when they died because the strap had no padding and bothered my bald head. My Bose headphones are much better (and they have padding on the strap YAY!!!!!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Sistema Microwave Cookware Easy Eggs</title>
			<link>/easyeggs/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
			<author>Baron Schwartz</author>
			<guid>/easyeggs/</guid>
			<description>&lt;p&gt;Rates very high on the suck-o-meter. First, getting the eggs to not be gross is near to impossible, and even worse, the stupid thing exploded in the microwave on the 3rd attempt to make eggs. End result, an egg disaster all over the microwave that took an hour to clean. You can make a lot of eggs in an hour which would have been a lot easier than trying to make eggs with this awful device.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
